[
 { "question": "mē", "answer": "me", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "quid", "answer": "what", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "nihil", "answer": "nothing", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "nōn", "answer": "not", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "saepe", "answer": "often", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "sī", "answer": "if", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "amō", "answer": "to love", "parts": "amāre, amāvī, amātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "amābō te", "answer": "please", "parts": "", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "cōgitō", "answer": "to think", "parts": "cōgitāre, cōgitāvī, cōgitātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "dēbeō", "answer": "to ought", "parts": "dēbēre, dēbuī, dēbitum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "dō", "answer": "to give", "parts": "dare, dedī, datum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "errō", "answer": "to go astray", "parts": "errāre, errāvī, errātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "laudō", "answer": "to praise", "parts": "laudāre, laudāvī, laudātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "moneō", "answer": "to advise", "parts": "monēre, monuī, monitum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "salveō", "answer": "to be well", "parts": "salvēre", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "salvē", "answer": "hello", "parts": "salvēte", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "servō", "answer": "to guard", "parts": "servāre, servāvī, servātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "cōnservō", "answer": "to preserve", "parts": "cōnservāre, cōnservāvī, cōnservātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "terreō", "answer": "to frighten", "parts": "terrēre, terruī, territum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "valeō", "answer": "to be strong", "parts": "valēre, valuī, valitūrum",  "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "valē", "answer": "goodbye", "parts": "valēte", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "videō", "answer": "to see", "parts": "vidēre, vīdī, vīsum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "vocō", "answer": "to call", "parts": "vocāre, vocāvī, vocātum", "lesson": 1 },
 { "question": "fāma", "answer": "reputation", "parts": "fāmae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "fōrma", "answer": "form", "parts": "fōrmae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "fortūna", "answer": "fortune", "parts": "fortūnae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "īra", "answer": "anger", "parts": "īrae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "nauta", "answer": "sailor", "parts": "nautae, m.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "patria", "answer": "fatherland", "parts": "patriae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "pecūnia", "answer": "money", "parts": "pecūniae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "philosophia", "answer": "philosophy", "parts": "philosophiae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "poena", "answer": "punishment", "parts": "poenae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "poenās dare", "answer": "to pay the penalty", "parts": "", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "poēta", "answer": "poet", "parts": "poētae, m.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "porta", "answer": "gate", "parts": "portae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "puella", "answer": "girl", "parts": "puellae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 {"question": "rosa", "answer": "rose", "parts": "rosae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "sententia", "answer": "opinion", "parts": "sententiae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "vīta", "answer": "life", "parts": "vītae, f.", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "antīquus", "answer": "ancient", "parts": "antīqua, antīquum", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "magnus", "answer": "large", "parts": "magna, magnus", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "meus", "answer": "my", "parts": "mea, meum", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "multus", "answer": "many", "parts": "multa, multum", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "tuus", "answer": "your", "parts": "tua, tuum", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "et", "answer": "and",  "parts": "",  "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "sed", "answer": "but", "parts": "", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "Ō", "answer": "Oh!", "parts": "", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "sine", "answer": "without", "parts": "", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "sum", "answer": "to be", "parts": "esse, fuī, futūrum", "lesson": 2 },
 { "question": "ager", "answer": "field", "parts": "agrī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "agricola", "answer": "farmer" , "parts": "agricolae, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "amīca", "answer": "friend", "parts": "amīcae, f.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "amīcus", "answer": "friend", "parts": "amīcī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "fēmina", "answer": "woman", "parts": "fēminae, f.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "fīlia", "answer": "daughter", "parts": "fīliae, f.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "fīlius", "answer": "son", "parts": "fīliī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "numerus", "answer": "number", "parts": "numerī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "populus", "answer": "the people", "parts": "populī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "puer", "answer": "boy", "parts": "puerī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "sapientia", "answer": "wisdom", "parts": "sapientiae, f.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "vir", "answer": "man", "parts": "virī, m.", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "avārus", "answer": "greedy", "parts": "avāra, avārum", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "paucī", "answer": "few", "parts": "paucae, pauca", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "Rōmānus", "answer": "Roman", "parts": "Rōmāna, Rōmānum", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "dē", "answer": "from", "parts": "", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "in", "answer": "in", "parts": "", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "hodiē", "answer": "today", "parts": "", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "semper", "answer": "always", "parts": "", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "habeō", "answer": "to have", "parts": "habēre, habuī, habitum", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "satiō", "answer": "to satisfy", "parts": "satiāre, satiāvī, satiātum", "lesson": 3 },
 { "question": "bāsium", "answer": "kiss", "parts": "bāsiī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "bellum", "answer": "war", "parts": "bellī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "cōnsilium", "answer": "plan", "parts": "cōnsiliī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "cūra", "answer": "care", "parts": "cūrae, f.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "dōnum", "answer": "gift", "parts": "dōnī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "exitium", "answer": "destruction", "parts": "exitiī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "magister", "answer": "teacher", "parts": "magistrī, m.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "magistra", "answer": "teacher", "parts": "magistrae, f.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "mora", "answer": "delay", "parts": "morae, f.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "nihil", "answer": "nothing", "parts": "n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "oculus", "answer": "eye", "parts": "oculī, m.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "officium", "answer": "duty", "parts": "officiī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "ōtium", "answer": "leisure", "parts": "ōtiī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "perīculum", "answer": "danger", "parts": "perīculī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "remedium", "answer": "cure", "parts": "remediī, n.", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "bellus", "answer": "pretty", "parts": "bella, bellum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "bonus", "answer": "good", "parts": "bona, bonum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "hūmānus", "answer": "human", "parts": "hūmāna, hūmānum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "malus", "answer": "bad", "parts": "mala, malum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "parvus", "answer": "small", "parts": "parva, parvum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "stultus", "answer": "foolish", "parts": "stulta, stultum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "vērus", "answer": "true", "parts": "vēra, vērum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "iuvō", "answer": "to help", "parts": "iuvāre, iūvī, iūtum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "adiuvō", "answer": "to help", "parts": "adiuvāre, adiūvī, adiūtum", "lesson": 4 },
 { "question": "adulēscentia", "answer": "youth", "parts": "adulēscentiae, f.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "animus", "answer": "soul", "parts": "animī, m.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "animī", "answer": "courage", "parts": "animōrum, m.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "caelum", "answer": "sky", "parts": "caelī, n.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "culpa", "answer": "blame", "parts": "culpae, f.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "glōria", "answer": "glory", "parts": "glōriae, f.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "verbum", "answer": "word", "parts": "verbī, n.", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "tē", "answer": "you", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "līber", "answer": "free", "parts": "lībera, līberum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "noster", "answer": "our", "parts": "nostra, nostrum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "pulcher", "answer": "beautiful", "parts": "pulchra, pulchrum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "sanus", "answer": "healthy", "parts": "sana, sanum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "igitur", "answer": "therefore", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "-ne", "answer": "?", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "propter", "answer": "because of", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "crās", "answer": "tomorrow", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "herī", "answer": "yesterday", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "quandō", "answer": "when", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "sī quandō", "answer": "if ever", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "satis", "answer": "enough", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "tum", "answer": "then", "parts": "", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "cēnō", "answer": "to dine", "parts": "cēnāre, cēnāvī, cēnātum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "culpō", "answer": "to blame", "parts": "culpāre, culpāvī, culpātum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "remaneō", "answer": "to remain", "parts": "remanēre, remānsī, remānsum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "maneō", "answer": "to stay", "parts": "manēre, mānsī, mānsum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "superō", "answer": "to be above", "parts": "superāre, superāvī, superātum", "lesson": 5 },
 { "question": "dea", "answer": "goddess", "parts": "deae, f.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "deus", "answer": "god", "parts": "deī, m.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "discipula", "answer": "student", "parts": "discipulae, f.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "discipulus", "answer": "student", "parts": "discipulī, m.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "īnsidiae", "answer": "ambush", "parts": "īnsidiārum, f.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "liber", "answer": "book", "parts": "librī, m.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "tyrannus", "answer": "tyrant", "parts": "tyrannī, m.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "vitium", "answer": "fault", "parts": "vitiī, n.", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "Graecus", "answer": "Greek", "parts": "Graeca, Graecum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "perpetuus", "answer": "continuous", "parts": "perpetua, perpetuum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "salvus", "answer": "safe", "parts": "salva, salvum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "secundus", "answer": "following", "parts": "secunda, secundum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "vester", "answer": "your", "parts": "vestra, vestrum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "-que", "answer": "and", "parts": "", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "ubi", "answer": "where", "parts": "", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "ibi", "answer": "there", "parts": "", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "nunc", "answer": "now", "parts": "", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "quārē", "answer": "therefore", "parts": "", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "possum", "answer": "to be able", "parts": "posse, potuī", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "tolerō", "answer": "to endure", "parts": "tolerāre, tolerāvī, tolerātum", "lesson": 6 },
 { "question": "amor", "answer": "love", "parts": "amōris, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "carmen", "answer": "song", "parts": "carminis, n.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "cīvitās", "answer": "state", "parts": "cīvitātis, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "corpus", "answer": "body", "parts": "corporis, n.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "homō", "answer": "human being", "parts": "hominis, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "labor", "answer": "work", "parts": "labōris, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "littera", "answer": "letter", "parts": "litterae, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "litterae", "answer": "literature", "parts": "litterārum, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "mōs", "answer": "habit", "parts": "mōris, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "mōrēs", "answer": "character", "parts": "mōrum, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "nōmen", "answer": "name", "parts": "nōminis, n.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "pāx", "answer": "peace", "parts": "pācis, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "rēgīna", "answer": "queen", "parts": "rēgīnae, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "rēx", "answer": "king", "parts": "rēgis, m.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "tempus", "answer": "time", "parts": "temporis, n.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "terra", "answer": "earth", "parts": "terrae, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "uxor", "answer": "wife", "parts": "uxōris, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "virgō", "answer": "maiden", "parts": "virginis, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "virtūs", "answer": "manliness", "parts": "virtūtis, f.", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "novus", "answer": "new", "parts": "nova, novum", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "post", "answer": "after", "parts": "", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "sub", "answer": "under", "parts": "", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "audeō", "answer": "to dare", "parts": "audēre, ausus sum", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "necō", "answer": "to murder", "parts": "necāre, necāvī, necātum", "lesson": 7 },
 { "question": "cōpia", "answer": "abundance", "parts": "cōpiae, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "cōpiae", "answer": "troops", "parts": "cōpiārum, f.", "lesson": 8 }, 
 { "question": "frāter", "answer": "brother", "parts": "frātris, m.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "laus", "answer": "praise", "parts": "laudis, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "lībertās", "answer": "liberty", "parts": "lībertātis, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "ratiō", "answer": "reason", "parts": "ratiōnis, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "scrīptor", "answer": "writer", "parts": "scrīptōris, m.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "soror", "answer": "sister", "parts": "sorōris, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "victōria", "answer": "victory", "parts": "victōriae, f.", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "dum", "answer": "while", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "ad", "answer": "to", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "ex", "answer": "from", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "ē", "answer": "from", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "numquam", "answer": "never", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "tamen", "answer": "nevertheless", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "agō", "answer": "to do", "parts": "agere, ēgī, āctum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "grātiās agere", "answer": "to give thanks", "parts": "", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "dēmōnstō", "answer": "to show", "parts": "dēmōnstrāre, dēmōnstrāvī, dēmōnstrātum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "discō", "answer": "to learn", "parts": "discere, didicī", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "doceō", "answer": "to teach", "parts": "docēre, docuī, doctum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "dūcō", "answer": "to lead", "parts": "dūcere, dūxī, ductum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "gerō", "answer": "to carry", "parts": "gerere, gessī, gestum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "scrībō", "answer": "to write", "parts": "scrībere, scrīpsī, scrīptum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "trahō", "answer": "to draw", "parts": "trahere, trāxī, tractum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "vincō", "answer": "to conquer", "parts": "vincere, vīcī, victum", "lesson": 8 },
 { "question": "locus", "answer": "place", "parts": "locī, m.", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "loca", "answer": "region", "parts": "locōrum, n.", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "locī", "answer": "literary passages", "parts": "locōrum, m.", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "morbus", "answer": "disease", "parts": "morbī, m.", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "studium", "answer": "eagerness", "parts": "studiī, n.", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "hic", "answer": "this", "parts": "haec, hoc", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "ille", "answer": "that", "parts": "illa, illud", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "iste", "answer": "that", "parts": "ista, istud", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "alius", "answer": "other", "parts": "alia, aliud", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "alter", "answer": "altera, alterum", "parts": "altera, alterum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "neuter", "answer": "neither", "parts": "neutra, neutrum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "nūllus", "answer": "none", "parts": "nūlla, nūllum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "sōlus", "answer": "only", "parts": "sōla, sōlum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "tōtus", "answer": "whole", "parts": "tōta, tōtum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "ūllus", "answer": "any", "parts": "ūlla, ūllum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "ūnus", "answer": "one", "parts": "ūna, ūnum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "uter", "answer": "either", "parts": "utra, utrum", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "enim", "answer": "for", "parts": "", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "in", "answer": "into", "parts": "", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "nimis", "answer": "too much", "parts": "", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "nimium", "answer": "too much", "parts": "", "lesson": 9 },
 { "question": "amīcitia", "answer": "friendship", "parts": "amīcitiae, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "cupiditās", "answer": "desire", "parts": "cupiditātis, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "hōra", "answer": "hour", "parts": "hōrae, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "nātūra", "answer": "nature", "parts": "nātūrae, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "senectūs", "answer": "old age", "parts": "senectūtis, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "timor", "answer": "fear", "parts": "timōris, m.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "vēritās", "answer": "truth", "parts": "vēritātis, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "via", "anaswer": "way", "parts": "viae, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "voluptās", "answer": "pleasure", "parts": "voluptātis, f.", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "beātus", "answer": "happy", "parts": "beāta, beātum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "quoniam", "answer": "since", "parts": "", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "cum", "answer": "with", "parts": "", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "audiō", "answer": "to hear", "parts": "audīre, audīvī, audītum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "capiō", "answer": "to take", "parts": "capere, cēpi, captum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "dīcō", "answer": "to say", "parts": "dīcere, dīxī, dictum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "faciō", "answer": "to make", "parts": "facere, fēcī, factum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "fugiō", "answer": "to flee", "parts": "fugere, fūgī, fugitűrum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "veniō", "answer": "to come", "parts": "venīre, vēnī, ventum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "inveniō", "answer": "to find", "parts": "invenīre, invēnī, inventum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "vīvō", "answer": "to live", "parts": "vīvere, vīxī, vīctum", "lesson": 10 },
 { "question": "caput", "answer": "head", "parts": "capitis, n.", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "cōnsul", "answer": "consul", "parts": "cōnsulis, m.", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "nēmō", "answer": "nobody", "parts": "nūllīus, m./f.", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "ego", "answer": "I", "parts": "meī", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "tū", "answer": "you", "parts": "tuī", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "is", "answer": "he", "parts": "eius", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "ea", "answer": "she", "parts": "eius", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "id", "answer": "it", "parts": "eius", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "īdem", "answer": "the same", "parts": "eadem, idem", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "amīcus", "answer": "friendly", "parts": "amīca, amīcum", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "cārus", "answer": "dear", "parts": "cāra, cārum", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "quod", "answer": "because", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "neque", "answer": "nor", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "nec", "answer": "nor", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "autem", "answer": "however", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "bene", "answer": "well", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "etiam", "answer": "also", "parts": "", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "intellegō", "answer": "to understand", "parts": "intellegere, intellēxī, intellēctum", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "mittō", "answer": "to send", "parts": "mittere, mīsī, missum", "lesson": 11 },
 { "question": "sentiō", "answer": "to feel", "parts": "sentīre, sēnsī, sēnsum", "lesson": 11 }
]
